It's normal for our bodies to not always be in tip-top condition, whether we catch the flu, have aching muscles after lots of exercise or get travel sick.
我们的身体并不总是处于最佳状态，无论是得了流感、大量运动后肌肉酸痛，还是晕车，这都是正常的。
But there's an ingredient that can help with all of that, and it can be used in all sorts of ways.
但有一种成分可以帮助缓解所有这些不适，而且它可以以各种方式被使用。
Ginger isn't just something to have in the kitchen – it's been used as an aid for centuries.
生姜不仅仅是厨房里的调味品——它作为治疗辅助品已有数百年历史。
Research consistently shows it eases nausea, such as motion sickness, and is recommended as a remedy by the NHS for helping ease pregnancy sickness.
研究一致表明，它可以缓解恶心，例如晕动病，英国国家医疗服务体系也推荐将其作为缓解孕吐的疗法。
Anna Daniels, a dietitian and spokesperson for the British Dietetic Association, says it's so beneficial because it has "powerful anti-inflammatory properties which assist with reducing inflammation in the gastrointestinal tract and therefore relieve discomfort and settle upset stomachs."
英国饮食协会发言人、营养师安娜·丹尼尔斯说，生姜之所以如此有益，是因为它具有"强大的抗炎特性，有助于减少胃肠道的炎症，从而缓解不适并安抚肠胃不适。"
And it can help with more than just nausea.
还有，它不仅能帮助缓解恶心。
Ginger tea has been shown to help fight colds and flu because it encourages perspiration, which in turn reduces feverish symptoms.
姜茶已被证明有助于对抗感冒和流感，因为它能促进排汗，从而减轻发烧症状。
Gingerol, a bioactive compound in the spice, has been found to help reduce the risk of infections because it supports immune health, including autoimmune conditions such as rheumatoid arthritis and lupus.
姜辣素是姜这种香料中的一种生物活性化合物，已被发现有助于降低感染风险，因为它能强化免疫健康，包括类风湿性关节炎和狼疮等自身免疫性疾病。
And if you're sporty, there's good news for you too.
如果你喜欢运动，同样也有好消息。
Studies by the International Journal of Preventative Medicine and The Journal of Pain found that a daily supplement of ginger eased muscle soreness after intense physical activity.
《国际预防医学杂志》和《疼痛杂志》的研究发现，每日补充生姜可以缓解剧烈运动后的肌肉酸痛。
So, how can you use ginger?
那么，如何使用生姜呢？
It's an incredibly versatile ingredient and can be used in almost anything from tea to biscuits to fiery stir-fries.
它是一种用途极其广泛的食材，几乎可以用于任何食物，从茶到饼干，再到辛辣的炒菜。
Many cafes and supermarkets now sell ginger shots promoting health benefits.
许多咖啡馆和超市现在都出售促进健康的姜汁饮品。
Emily Jonzen, author of The Goodness of Ginger and Turmeric, suggests grating it, though she advises "it has a strong flavour and a fieriness to it so introduce it to your cooking a little at a time".
《生姜和姜黄的益处》一书的作者艾米丽·琼森建议将生姜磨碎，不过她提醒说："它味道浓郁，而且辛辣，所以一次少量地加入你的烹饪中。"
So, if you like the taste, you could incorporate it into your diet and see if you feel these health benefits.
所以，如果你喜欢它的味道，可以将其融入你的饮食中，看看是否能感受到这些健康益处。